Guide to the Multicultural Student Services Center records, 1969-2016 RG0056
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Multicultural Student Services Center, 1969-1993; 1980-1993; RG0056 Series 1
  - Thompson, Terri, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Yu, Ken, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Zamoff, Mitchell, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - GWU Updated HI/SCIP Participants, 1985-1986, 1986 Spring; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Adams, Michelle, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Bailey, Dionne, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Bergmann, Elizabeth, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Brennan, Dana, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Brooks, Kenneth, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Caton, Scott, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Ashe, Kevin, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Clay, Caroline, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Cox, Margit, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Cogley, Jennifer, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Dantley, Teresa, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Davidson, Danny, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Dickey, Christin, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Doniger, Kijo, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Evans, Shari, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Gessner, Damian, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Hill, Nancy, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Johnson, Heather, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Litton, Mark, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Mathews, Lisa, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Mays, David, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Messina, Ann Kathryn, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Olsen, Nils, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Amy Parker, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Parker, Leslie, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Povich, Lisa, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Quinn, Rusden, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Raskin, Stephen, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Risser, John, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Schaller, Susanna, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Stechschulte, Katherine, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Tayor, Katherine, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Tyler, Darcey, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Wells, Tomiko, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Williams, Adrienne, 1985-1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Davidson, Danny, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Branch, Dawana, 1987 February 26; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Schwarte, Hilary, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Turner, Catharyn, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Cartland, Marshall, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Charles, Jennifer, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Chen, Patrick, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Chesky, Pamela, 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Coble, Sheila, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Cohen, David, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Coplan, David, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Cormeny, Sara, 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Devall, Carrie, 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - McLeod, Tracy, 1986-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Greene, Nathaniel, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Greenberger, Scott, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Groberg, David, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Harrington, Roxanne, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Harris, Bonnie, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Hobso, Rosalyn, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Howell, Marya, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - [Alix Koromzay], 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Paddack, Michelle, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Sharkey, Michael, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Thomas, Wendall, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Thompson, Crystal, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - HI/SCIP Participants, 1984-1985, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Class Entering 1970: Grades, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Class Entering 1969 [1/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Class Entering 1969 [2/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Class Entering 1968: EOP Grades, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Class Entering 1968, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - HISCIP Students, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - HISCIP Students, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - HISCIP Students, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - HISCIP Students, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - New Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Demographics, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at GWU, Summer 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Student Demographics Report, 1984-1985, September 24, 1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) at The George Washington University, February 10, 1975; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rita Bailey's Temporary Employee Time Sheets, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Contains social security numbers.
  - Test file: List of contents, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Tutorial Directory, 1979-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Washington Area Library Guide, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Work Report Blank Forms, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - HI/SCIP Grade Information, 1979-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - HI/SCIP Grade Information, 1979-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Ahuruezenma Anytonnu's Temporary Employee Time Sheets, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Folder included documents with social security numbers.
  - The Educational Opportunity Program's (EOP) Annual Report for 1985-1986, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Public Library Film Index, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Reunion/ 10th Anniversary for The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Manual, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Senate Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Personnel (Past Staff) General Correspondence, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    General correspondence
  - Nuclear Medicine Curriculum, Fall 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Professional Development, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Graduates, Fall 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Gail Brinnie Medley's Acceptance Letter, June 15, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Peer Counseling Interview Sheets, March 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Ms. Pridgen Financial Aid Form Correspondence, March 30, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Education 009: Spring Offerings, January 14, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Arrangements for First Thursday at the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), January 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial Aid (1983-84) and the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Recruitment Plans, January 24, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Guide to the Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Office Calendar of Staff Objectives: Addendum Copy, October 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Classification Descriptions, 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Job Descriptions include: 1) Director, Educational Opportunity Program (EOP); 2) Assistant Director, Educational Opportunity Program (EOP); 3) Senior Stenographer-Secretary; and 4) Senior Secretary.
  - Responsibilities Delegated at 4-15-76 Meeting, April 15, 1976; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - University Policy on the Release of Student Information, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Career Services/Guidelines for Writing and Interpreting Recommendation Statements, March 13, 1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Student Interview Guidelines, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Georgetown Medical: Dental Health Careers Program, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - What TV Does to Kids, February 21, 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - The New Racism, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Affirmative Action Plans, 1974-1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - University of Maryland Report of Admission and Retention of Minority Students in Large Universities, 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Materials, 1970-1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - A Minority Students Career Symposium, March 1970; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC) Department Files [1 of 3], 1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    This folder includes documents related to the Education Opportunity Center, job applications,"Counseling Black Individuals: Some Stereotypes," the Annual Report of the Committee on University and Urban Affairs, EOP Director and Counselor Goals, The Black People's Union, and the Student Organizations Budget Proposal.
  - Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC) Department Files [2 of 3], 1977-1981; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    This folder contains documents related to the University Policy on Academic Dishonesty, EOP Students Class of 1978, Personnelite: College and University Personnel Association, Self-Evaluation of the Division of Student Affairs, EOP Recruitment/Open House, EOP Advisory Committee Meeting, and EOP Student Interview Guidelines.
  - Multicultural Student Services Center (MSSC) Department Files [3 of 3], 1979-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    This folder contains documents related to the Report on "Practical Applications of Study Techniques," EOP Office Manual, Application for Graduation forms, EOP Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at GW, and transcript request forms.
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at The George Washington University, Summer 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Offers of Financial Aid, April 24, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Restricted as folder includes details about financial aid recipients.
  - The Educational Opportunity Program (EOP) Quick Reference Guide to Academic Procedures at The George Washington University, Summer 1986; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Application and Graduation Materials, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Folder includes materials entitled: 1) Application for Graduation; 2) HI/SCIP Admission Requirements; 3) Tuition Fees at 2,660 Colleges and Universities, 1984-1985; 4) Career Awareness 85' Week; 5) 1984-85 National Student Teaching Competition; 6) PREP Math Syllabus for Independent Study Group; and 7) Syllabus - Writing Skills.
  - Mailing Addresses, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Columbian College of Arts and Sciences List of Students, Undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) Students SAT and LSAT Scores, September 1, 1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Per FERPA, SAT and LSAT scores are restricted.
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) Roster, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Per FERPA, access to this folder is restricted due to the inclusion of social security numbers.
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) Demographics Report, 1984-1985, September 24, 1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) at The George Washington University: A Report on the First Five Years, 1969-1974, February 10, 1975; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - The Education Opportunity Program (EOP) Student Data, Summer 1978 - Spring 1979, June 1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    Per FERPRA, the folder's contents are restricted as the materials detail student's SAT scores.
  - EOP Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes '83, 1983-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 1)
  - EOP Advisory Committee Meeting Minues '82, 1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 2)
  - 1984-85 EOP Advisory Committee, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Budget Request, 1979-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 4)
  - Academic Year, 1982-83, 1982-1983; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 5)
  - Academic Year, 1981-82, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 6)
  - Academic Year, 1980-1981, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 7)
  - Academic Year, 1979-1980, 1979 October 12; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 8)
  - Academic Year, 1978-1979, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 9)
  - EOP Advisory Committee on Academic Support, 1970-1975; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1969-70, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 11)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1970-71, 1970-1971; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 12)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1971-72, 1971-1972; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 13)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1973-74, 1973-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 14)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1972-73, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 15)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting, Minutes, 1974-75, 1974-1975; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 16)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1975-76, 1975-1976; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 17)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1976-77, 1976-1977; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 18)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1977-78, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 19)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1978-79, 1978-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 20)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1979-80, 1979-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 21)
  - Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 22)
  - D.L.R. Monthly Report FY (July and September) 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 23)
  - M.B Monthly Report FY 1987-88, 1987 September; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 24)
  - D.L.R. Incoming Correspondence F 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 25)
  - D.L.R. Outgoing Correspondence FY 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 26)
  - V.L.E. Monthly Report FY 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 27)
  - Journalism Job Opportunity Conference and GW Pride Correspondence, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 28)
  - EOP Annual Report, 1986-87 [1/2], 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 29)
  - EOP Annual Report, 1986-87 [2/2], 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 30)
  - EOP Advisory Committee Information FY 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 31)
  - EOP Employment Applications, 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 32)
  - Report of the Committee on Coordinated Planning, 1988 May; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 33)
  - AETNA Life and Casualty Foundation, 1987 November; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 34)
  - General MSSC Materials (1 of 2), 1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 35)
  - General MSSC Materials (2 of 2), 1985-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 36)
  - V.L.E. Incoming Correspondence FY 87-88, 1986-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 37)
  - V.L.E. Outgoing Correspondence FY 87-88, 1987-1989; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 38)
  - Building Policy/Room Reservation FY 1987-88, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 39)
  - Room Reservations FY 1987-88, 1987-1988; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 40)
  - Advisory Committee materials, 1986-1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 41)
  - United House of Prayer for all People Incoming Correspondence, 1984 January 30; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 42)
  - EOP Office Concerns, 1971-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 43)
  - Building HH Concens, 1981-1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 44)
  - Minutes - Staff Meetings, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 45)
  - Jones, Destinie, 1987; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 46)
  - EOP Office Calenda of Staff Objectives, 1984 October; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 47)
  - Office Manual 1984 In Progress, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 48)
  - EOP Monthly Reports, 1984-1985; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 49)
  - Peer Conselor Training Manual, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 50)
  - PREP [Pre-College Review and Enrichment Program Schedule and materials], 1984, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10A, Folder 51)
  - PREP (Box 10A, Folder 1)
    - Peer counselor training manual (Box 10A, Folder 2)
    - EOP monthly reports (Box 10A, Folder 3)
    - Office manual, 1984 (Box 10A, Folder 4)
    - EOP office calendar (Box 10A, Folder 5)
    - Staff meeting minutes (Box 10A, Folder 6)
    - Building HH concerns (Box 10A, Folder 7)
    - Incoming correspondence (Box 10A, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing correspondence (Box 10A, Folder 9)
    - Room reservations (Box 10A, Folder 10)
    - Building policy (Box 10A, Folder 11)
    - Employment (Box 10A, Folder 12)
    - EOP Advisory committee (Box 10A, Folder 13)
    - EOP Annual report, 1986-1987 (Box 10A, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 10A, Folder 15)
    - AC, 1980-1981 (Box 10A, Folder 16)
    - AC, 1970-1971 (Box 10A, Folder 17)
    - AC, 1969-1970 (Box 10A, Folder 18)
    - AC, 1971-1972 (Box 10A, Folder 19)
    - AC, 1973-1974 (Box 10A, Folder 20)
    - AC, 1972-1973 (Box 10A, Folder 21)
    - Academic year, 1978-1979 (Box 10A, Folder 22)
    - Academic year, 1979-1980 (Box 10A, Folder 23)
    - Academic year, 1980-1981 (Box 10A, Folder 24)
    - Academic year, 1981-1982 (Box 10A, Folder 25)
    - EOP advisory committee meeting, 1983 (Box 10A, Folder 26)
  - [Drawer list of Multicultural Student Services Center materials ?], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 1)
  - EOP Entering Students 1984 Report / Original Cop, RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 2)
  - Campus Directory, George Washington University Full-Time Administrative and Instructional Staff, 1981-82, 1981-1982; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 3)
  - Student Grade Sheets [1/2], 1968-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 4)
  - Student Grade Sheets [2/2], 1968-1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 5)
  - [Copies of "The Monda Report," "The Hatchet," and "Open University of Washington", 1980; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 6)
  - College Entrance Examination Board School Code List, 1975-76, 1975-1976; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 7)
  - ["Folder Out" Cards], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 8)
  - Rough Draft Folder [Information on EOP Students], 1983-1984, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 9)
  - [Correspondence from Ronald L. Whitemore, EOP Director], 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 10)
  - [Time Sheet materials], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 11)
  - George Washington University Student Association Student Directory, 1978-79, 1978-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 10B, Folder 12)
  - Class Entering 1970 [1/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 1)
  - Class Entering 1970 [2/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 2)
  - Class Entering 1971 [1/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 3)
  - Class Entering 1971 [2/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 4)
  - Class Entering 1972 [1/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1972 [2/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 6)
  - Class Entering 1973 [1/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 7)
  - Class Entering 1973 [2/2], undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 8)
  - Class Entering 1974, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 9)
  - Class Entering 1975, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 10)
  - Class Entering 1976, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 11)
  - Class Entering 1977, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 12)
  - Class Entering 1978, undated; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 13)
  - [Hunt, William, 68-69], 1974-1975, 1978; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 14)
  - Hardin, Robert (SOS), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 15)
  - Foster, Leo (SOS), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 16)
  - Hester, Shelia (SOS), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 17)
  - Johnson, Sandra (SOS), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 18)
  - Russell, Vernon (SOS), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 19)
  - Bell, Gerald, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 20)
  - Blackburn, Sylvia, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 21)
  - Douglas, Deidre, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 22)
  - Hall, Maria, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 23)
  - Dickinson, Arnisha, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 24)
  - Love, Kenneth, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 25)
  - Manning, Lillian, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 26)
  - McDowell, Sandra, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 27)
  - Parker, Phyllis, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 28)
  - Tate, Harold, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 29)
  - Tyler, Arthur, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 30)
  - Brice, Maria, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 31)
  - Brock, Kenneth, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 32)
  - Hagan, Elizabeth, 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 33)
  - Ivey, Gloria (Fall '71), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 34)
  - Ivey, Linda (Sum 76), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 35)
  - Johnson, Melissa (Fall 73), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 36)
  - Kibler, Constance (Sp 73), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 37)
  - Minor, Sharon (Fall 69), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 38)
  - West, Edith (Fall 72), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 39)
  - Worthy, Jacqueline (Fall 71), 1968; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 40)
  - Simmonds, Kirth, 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 41)
  - Robinson, Lamar, 1969-1975; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, Esther, 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 43)
  - Newman, Constance, 1969-1973; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 44)
  - Mills, Sheila, 1969-1974; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 45)
  - Gullatt, Deborah, 1969-1979; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 46)
  - Toatley, Joseph, 1969; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 47)
  - 1982-1983 Student Financial Aid Mailing Labels [1/2], RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 48)
  - 1982-1983 Student Financial Aid Mailing Labels [2/2], RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 49)
  - Gamble, James, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 50)
  - Isaacs, Lisa Renee, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 51)
  - Janney, Eli, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 52)
  - Johns, Timothy Alan, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 53)
  - Johnson, Cheryl D., 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 54)
  - Lee, Michael, 1984 June 27; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 55)
  - Lee, Rose June, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 56)
  - Lewis, Latonia, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 57)
  - Martinez, Ana Ludivina, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 58)
  - Middleton, William Tyrone, 1984; RG0056 Series 1 (Box 11A, Folder 59)